{
    "subject": "resource/Hellville_de_Luxe",
    "predicate": "property/artist",
    "object": "Enrique Bunbury",
    "human_readable": "The artist of Hellville de Luxe is Enrique Bunbury.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7651708722114563,
            "question": "Who is the artist behind the album 'Hellville de Luxe'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7109150290489197,
            "question": "Has Enrique Bunbury won any awards for his work on 'Hellville de Luxe'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.435666561126709,
            "question": "Are there any notable collaborations on the album 'Hellville de Luxe'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4133586585521698,
            "question": "What is the name of the album created by Enrique Bunbury?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3858794867992401,
            "question": "What other albums has Enrique Bunbury released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35605332255363464,
            "question": "What musical genre does 'Hellville de Luxe' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34544846415519714,
            "question": "Enrique Bunbury is known for which type of musical work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34533146023750305,
            "question": "Is 'Hellville de Luxe' a solo project or part of a band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3161556124687195,
            "question": "How was the album 'Hellville de Luxe' received by music critics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31113871932029724,
            "question": "What is the overall theme or message conveyed in 'Hellville de Luxe'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The artist of Hellville de Luxe is Enrique Bunbury.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1269_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How was the album 'Hellville de Luxe' received by music critics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1269_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Hellville de Luxe' a solo project or part of a band?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1269_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Enrique Bunbury is known for which type of musical work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1269_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1269_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1269_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1269_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1269_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1269_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1269_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1269_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1269_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1269_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1269_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After reviewing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention several times that \"Hellville De Luxe\" is an album by Enrique Bunbury."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that \"The artist of Hellville De Luxe is Enrique Bunbury.\" This can be inferred from multiple mentions within the context, such as \"Enrique Bunbury continues to pursue his solo career in Hellville De Luxe\" and details about the album's production and reception."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}